President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of H. Patrick Swygert Records, 1977-1998; 13; 100 cubic ft.
  - UUP, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Women's Groups, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - World Food Day, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - World Week, 1991; 1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Writers Institute, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Writers Institute, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Registrar, 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Rerum Novarum, Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Research Office, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Salaries, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Salaries, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Search- Arts and Sciences Dean(Confidential), Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Search- Athletic Director(Confidential), Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Search- School of Education Dean(Confidential), Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Seate Higher Education Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Smoking Policy, Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Space, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Space, Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Student Accounts, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Student Association, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Student Association, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Student Association, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Student Association Constitution, Undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Student Association Legal Services, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Student Association Legal Services, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Schenectady County Community College, Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Travel, Undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Travel Agency Selection Committee, Undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Institute of Public Administration, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Minority Issues in Higher Education, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Minority Retention, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - NASULGC, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - NASULGC, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - NASULGC, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - National Association for Equal Opportunity in Higher Education, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - New Faculty/Professional staff, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - New Faculty/Professional staff, 1991 September (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - New Faculty/Professional staff, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - New Faculty- Women's Reception, 1992 November 20 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - New York Council for the Humanities, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - New York Council for the Humanities, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - New York State Education Department, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Academic Calendar, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Academic Calendar, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - American Council on Education, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - American Council on Education, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Admissions, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Admissions, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Advocacy, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action Sexual Harassment, Undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Association, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Association, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - American Red Cross, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Athletics, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Budget Accounting, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Budget Accounting, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Budget Accounting, 1990 January 8-1990 August 23 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Budget Accounting, 1990 September 4-1990 September 12 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Center for Environmental Sciences and Technology Management CESTM Design Committee: Architect Selection, Undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Design Committee file, Stephen E. DeLong, Special Assistant to the President, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Statements of Qualification, submitted by architectural firms responding to the solicitation by the Design Committee, Undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Presentations by the four finalist firms to the Design Committee, KeyCorp, 1993 September 13 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Presentations by the four finalist firms to Officers of the University at Albany, 1993 September 28 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Photographs (including negatives) of buildings designed by three of the finalist firms (Cannon, EYP, Wm. Hall); taken by Stephen E. DeLong during visits in 8/93&9/93, 1993 August-1993 September (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Budget Panels, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Budget Planning, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Budget Waiver Forms, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Budget Waiver Forms, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - China Exchange, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Citizen Bee, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Columbus Quicentenary, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Commencement, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Commencement, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Commencement-December Graduates Assembly, Undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Honors Convocation, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Honors Convocation, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Computer Allocations, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Disability Students, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Disability Students, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Diversity, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - EOP, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - ECC, 1986-1990 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Empire State Games, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Employee assistance Program, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Enrollment, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Enrollment, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Enrollment, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Billington, James, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Pelikan, Jaroslav, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Human Resources, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Inauguration Invitations, Undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Inauguration, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Information Systems & Technology, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Arts in Education, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Health Care Management, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Alicia de Colombi-Manguio (Piancia, Zitelli) (Confidential), Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Search - Coordinator Public/Community Events, Undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - School of Business, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - School of Public Health, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - School of Public Health, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - School of Public Health-Affiliation Arguments, Undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - School of Public Health-- Convocation, 1990 April 25 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Bus Fee, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Business Advisory Council, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - By-Laws, Schools & Colleges, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Calendar, Summer, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Campus Safety for Women, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Campus Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Campus Life, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Capital Area School Development Association, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Capital Area School Development Association, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Center for Arts & Humanities, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - ReReading - Report, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Computing & Disability, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Center for Excellence in Science & Math Education, Undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Chapel House, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Convocation, 1980-1989 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Convocation, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - EOP, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Financial Aid, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Financial Aid, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Financial Aid, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Fire Alarms, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - First Cities, Undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Foreign Visitors, Undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Formal Greetings, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Fraternities, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Freedom of Expression, 1983-1989 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Freshmen, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - General Education, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - General Education, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - General Education, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - General Electric, 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - General Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Gifts, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Governors Office, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Health Center, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Health Center, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Health Center, 1980-1990 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Hispanic & Italian Studies, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Homecoming/Parents, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - ACUSNY, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Alcohol, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Alcohol, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Athletics, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Athletics Board - Intercollegiate, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Benevolent Association, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Budget Planning, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Center for Research & Learning, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Commercial Activities, Undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Council of Deans, 1986-1990 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Employee Assistance Program, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Excelsior Awards, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Apartment, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Apartment, 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Workload, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Field House, Undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Library, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Library, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - New York State Legislature, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - New York State Theatre Institute, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Parent's Weekend, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Parking Policy, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Parking Policy, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Performance Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Personnel, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Personnel, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Plant Department, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Plant Department, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Presidential & Frederick Douglass Scholars, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Presidential & Frederick Douglass Scholars, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - President's Task Force on Women's Safety, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Public Safety, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Public Safety, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Purple & Gold, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Purple & Gold, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Academic Programs, Policy & Planning, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Administrator's Retreat, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Administrator's Retreat, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Administrator's Retreat, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action, 1986-1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Chancellor, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Chancellor, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Chancellor, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Chancellor's Forum, 1992 April 5-1992 April 7 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Chancellor's Forum, 1991 April 29-1991 April 30 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Administrator's Retreat, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Council of Presidents, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Council of Presidents, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Council of Presidents, 1991 January 23 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Council of Presidents, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Evaluation of Presidents, Undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Executive Vice Chancellor, Undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Finance and Business, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Finance and Business, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Finance and Business, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Finance and Business, 1986-1989 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Institutional Research & Analytical Studies, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Relations (Governmental Relations), 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Relations (Governmental Relations), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Provost, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Provost, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Provost, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Research Foundation, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Research Foundation, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Research Foundation, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Research and Graduate Studies, Undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - SUNY Senior Vice Chancellor Harry K. Spindler, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Senior Vice Chancellor, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Special Program, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Special Program, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Special Programs, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Commission - Testimony, Undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - SUNY Construction Fund, Undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - SUNY Faculty Senate, Undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - University Counsel (Confidential), 1992 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - University Counsel (Confidential), 1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - University Counsel (Confidential), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - University Relations Alumni Development, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - University Affairs/Development, Undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - SUNY 2000, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - SUNY 2000, Undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - SUNY Task Group on System Restructuring, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Educational Services, Undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Distinguished Citizen Awards, Undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Planning Documents Administrative Planning Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Planning Documents Administrative Planning Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Budget Panel Finance and Business, 1992 April 19 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Budget Panel Presidents Area Presentation, 1992 April 9 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Budget Panel Research and Graduate Studies Presentation, 1992 April 6 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Budget Panel Student Affairs Presentation, 1992 April 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Budget Panel University Advancement Presentation, 1992 March 30 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Budget Panel Academic Affairs Presentation - Academic Support Services, 1992 April 16 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Budget Panel Academic Affairs Presentation - Rockefeller College, 1992 April 19 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Budget Panel Academic Affairs Presentation - Academic Support Services, 1992 April 14 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Budget Panel Academic Affairs Presentation - Rockefeller College, 1992 April 14 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Budget Panel Academic Affairs Presentation, 1992 May 11 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Budget Panel Academic Affairs Presentation - Humanities and Fine Art, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Budget Panel Draft Report, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Budget Panel Report Corrections, 1992 February 20 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Budget Panel Final Report, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Budget Panel Handouts at First Meeting, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Budget Panel Membership List and Meeting Schedule, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Budget Panel Subcommittee Materials, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Budget Panel Membership Schedule and Subcommittee List, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Budget Panel, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Budget Panel Final Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Budget Panel Final Draft, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Budget Panel Student Affairs Presentation, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Budget Panel University Advancement Presentation, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Budget Panel Finance and Business Presentation, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Budget Panel Academic Affairs Presentation, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Budget Panel Research and Graduate Studies Presentation, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Budget Panel Presidents Area Presentation, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Budget Panel meeting Handouts, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Budget Panel, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Final Budget Request, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Accreditation - Other (Departments, etc.), 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - President Advisory Council for Alcohol and Drug Abuse Prevention, Undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - America Red Cross, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Originals, 1993 January 13 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Originals, 1992 December (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Meeting, 1992 November 13 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - United Way Priorities and Red Cross, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - America Red Cross Albany Area Chapter Strategic Planning Committee, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - America Red Cross Albany Area Chapter Organizational Meeting, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - America Red Cross Albany Area Chapter Organizational Meeting, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Organizational Meeting, 1992 October 27 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Originals, 1992 February (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Budget Request Final Narrative, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Budget Request Final Narrative, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Budget Request Final Narrative, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - CESTM, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - CESTM, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - CESTM, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - CESTM, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - CESTM, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - CESTM, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - CESTM, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - CESTM, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - CESTM, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - CESTM, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - CESTM, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - CESTM, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Academic Calendar, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Middle States Self Study for Reaccreditation, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - CESTM, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - CESTM, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - The Center for Environmental Sciences and Technology Management Prospects, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - ASRC Presentation at Victors Rileys KeyCorp, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Tech Met CESTM Article, 1992 December 11 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Budget - Speech Graphics and Slides, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - School of Business Profile, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - EPC Long Range Planning Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Joint Admissions Program, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - SUNY Enrollment Reports, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Undergraduate Admissions System, 1981-1985 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Application Inquiries, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Budget-Freeze, Restrictions, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Final Budget Request (Originals), 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Budget Request (Draft), 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Campus Closing, Undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Capital Campaign, Undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - CESTM(Center for Environment Science and Technology Management), 1993 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - CESTM Narrative-Original May, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Attachment A-Legislation-Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Attachment B- Tese Letter-Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Attachment C- Impact Study-Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Attachment D-Center Anticipated Payroll-Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Attachment E - Awards to Atmospheric Scientists - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Attachment F - Companies Involved with ASRC - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Attachment G - Potential Commercial Applications - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Attachment H- ASRC Press Coverage- Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Attachment I - X-Ray Optical System Benefits - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Attachment J - X-Ray Optics Press Coverage - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Attachment K - Advanced Materials Economic Development Thrust - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Attachment L - Advanced Materials Industrial Funding - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Attachment M - University at Albany Foundation Numbers - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Attachment N - Facility and Site Plan - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Attachment O - Cost Options - Original, Undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - VDC - APP, Undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Computer Information, Undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Economic Development 1991-1993, Undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Art Museum Director Search, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Campus and Community Safety, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Commission on University Athletics, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Freedom of Expression, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Education and Research, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Education and Research, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Education and Research(GRI), Undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Office, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Student Organization, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Student Organization, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Student Organization, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Studies, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Studies, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Studies, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Graduation Fee, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Grievance Procedures, 1972-1981 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Gulf Crisis, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Health Fee, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Health Fee, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Information Systems & Technology, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Institutional Research, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Institutional Research, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Internal Audit, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Internal Audit, Undated (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - International Programs, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - International Students, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Intersession Closing (President's Area), Undated (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Intersession Closing, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Intersession Closing, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Invitations, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Invitations, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Judicial System, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - King, Martin Luther Jr. Commission, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - King, Martin Luther Jr. Commission, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - King, Martin Luther King, Jr. Institute for Non-Violence, Undated (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - League of Women Voters Campaign Watch Committee, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Liberty Partnership Program, 1992; 1991 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Library, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Mayor of Albany, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Mayor of Albany, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Measles, 1987-1990 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Minority Student Services, 1988-1991 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Capital Facilities, Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Contracts and Purchase, Undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Doctoral Campuses President, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - SUNY Best Program, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - SUNY Construction Fund, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - SUNY Presidents Collective Bargaining Committee(UUP), Undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Senior Vice Chancellor, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - University Council, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - University Council, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - University Council, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - University Council, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - University Council, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - University Council, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - University Relations Alumni & Development, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - University Senate, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Association, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - School of Business, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Script, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Child Care, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Co-Curricular Committee on the Freshman Year Report and Recommendation, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - New York State Ethics Commission, Undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - SUNY 2000, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - SUNY 2000, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - SUNY 2000 Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - SUNY 2000 Task Force on Economic Development, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 12)